♪ ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I'M TRYNA PUT YOU
IN THE WORST MOOD ♪
♪ P1 CLEANER THAN
YOUR CHURCH SHOES ♪
♪ MILLI POINT 2 JUST
TO HURT YOU ♪
♪ ALL RED LAMB JUST
TO TEASE YOU ♪
♪ NONE OF THESE TOYS
ON LEASE TOO ♪
♪ MADE YOUR WHOLE
YEAR IN A WEEK TOO ♪
♪ MAIN BITCH OUT OF
YOUR LEAGUE TOO ♪
♪ SIDE BITCH OUT OF
♪ HOUSE SO EMPTY
NEED A CENTERPIECE ♪
♪ 20 RACKS A TABLE
CUT FROM EBONY ♪
♪ SHE CUT THAT IVORY
INTO SKINNY PIECES ♪
♪ THEN SHE CLEAN IT
WITH HER FACE MAN ♪
♪ I LOVE MY BABY ♪
♪ YOU TALKING MONEY
NEED A HEARING AID ♪
♪ YOU TALKING BOUT ME I
CAN'T SEE THE SHADE ♪
♪ SWITCH UP MY STYLE
I TAKE ANY LANE ♪
♪ SWITCH UP MY CUP
I KILL ANY PAIN ♪
♪♪♪
♪ LOOK WHAT YOU DONE! ♪
♪ I'M A MOTHER
FUCKIN STARBOY ♪
♪♪♪
♪ LOOK WHAT YOU DONE! ♪
♪ I'M A MOTHER
FUCKIN STARBOY ♪
♪ EVERY DAY A NIGGA
TRY TO TEST ME ♪
TRY TO END ME ♪
♪ PULL OFF IN THAT
ROADSTER SV ♪
♪ POCKETS OVER WEIGHT
GETTIN HEFTY ♪
♪ COMING FOR THE KING
THAT'S A FAR CRY ♪
♪ I COME ALIVE IN
THE FALL TIME ♪
♪ NO COMPETITION I
DON'T REALLY LISTEN ♪
♪ I'M IN THE BLUE MULSANNE
BUMPING NEW EDITION ♪
♪ HOUSE SO EMPTY NEED
A CENTERPIECE ♪
♪ 20 RACKS A TABLE
CUT FROM EBONY ♪
♪ SHE CUT THAT IVORY
INTO SKINNY PIECES ♪
♪ THEN SHE CLEAN IT
WITH HER FACE MAN ♪
♪ I LOVE MY BABY ♪
♪ YOU TALKING MONEY
NEED A HEARING AID ♪
♪ YOU TALKING BOUT ME I
CAN'T SEE THE SHADE ♪
♪ SWITCH UP MY STYLE
I TAKE ANY LANE ♪
♪ SWITCH UP MY CUP
I KILL ANY PAIN ♪
♪♪♪
♪ LOOK WHAT YOU DONE! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'M A MOTHER
FUCKIN STARBOY ♪
♪♪♪
♪ LOOK WHAT YOU DONE! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'M A MOTHER
FUCKIN STARBOY ♪
♪ LET A NIGGA BRAG PITT
LEGEND OF THE FALL ♪
♪ TOOK THE YEAR
LIKE A BANDIT ♪
♪ BOUGHT MOMMA A CRIB
AND A BRAND NEW WAGON ♪
♪ NOW SHE HIT THE GROCERY
SHOP LOOKIN LAVISH ♪
♪ STAR TREK ROOF IN
THAT WRAITH OF KHAN ♪
♪ GIRLS GET LOOSE WHEN
THEY HEAR THE SONG ♪
♪ 100 ON THE DASH GET
ME CLOSE TO GOD ♪
♪ WE DON'T PRAY FOR LOVE
WE JUST PRAY FOR CARS ♪
♪ HOUSE SO EMPTY NEED
A CENTERPIECE ♪
♪ 20 RACKS A TABLE CUT
FROM EBONY ♪
♪ SHE CUT THAT IVORY
INTO SKINNY PIECES ♪
♪ THEN SHE CLEAN IT
WITH HER FACE ♪
♪ MAN I LOVE MY BABY ♪
♪ YOU TALKING MONEY
NEED A HEARING AID ♪
♪ YOU TALKING BOUT ME I
CAN'T SEE THE SHADE ♪
♪ SWITCH UP MY STYLE
I TAKE ANY LANE ♪
♪ SWITCH UP MY CUP
I KILL ANY PAIN ♪
♪ ♪
♪ LOOK WHAT YOU DONE! ♪
♪ I'M A MOTHER
FUCKIN STARBOY ♪
♪♪♪
♪ LOOK WHAT YOU DONE! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'M A MOTHER
FUCKIN STARBOY ♪
♪♪♪
♪ LOOK WHAT YOU DONE! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'M A MOTHER
FUCKIN STARBOY ♪
♪♪♪
♪ LOOK WHAT YOU DONE! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'M A MOTHER
FUCKIN STARBOY ♪